Ereelance Programmer – Game Development

Al & Gameplay Programmer

Winter Park, FL - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/540f6f3ff9a7d335

An experienced developer with the ability to write efficient and effective code in many different programming languages. As well as being extremely knowledgeable in all avenues of programming and the technology industry; C++, C#, AI, Gameplay, Networking and Engine development. With many different project showing casing prime examples of path finding, AI and gameplay systems to achieve a complete product worth shipping to consumers.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Programmer - Game Development

UPWORK.COM - Orlando, FL - December 2015 to May 2016

Upwork is the premier platform for top companies to hire and work with the world's most talented independent professionals. Previously responsible for the oversight, development and project management for an iOS and Android platform game in development.

Sales and Customer Service Representative

Best Buy - Chesterfield, MO - October 2014 to December 2015

Partner with other employees to ensure customers' end-to-end needs for are met and that no customer is left unserved or undeserved. Provide friendly, fast, and accurate processing for all customer transactions at the front lanes and customer service while providing velocity solutions to customers.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Sciene in Game Development

Full Sail University - Orlando, FL August 2015 to June 2017

SKILLS

C# (2 years), C+ (2 years), Databases (1 year), DirectX (2 years), Engines (2 years), Al Programming (2 years)

LINKS

http://codebrosstudios.ddns.net

http://www.philipdsimpson.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/philipdsimpson/

AWARDS

Perfect Attendance Award

June 2017

Durring my time at Full sail I maintained a perfect attendance to all classes and labs.

Course Directors Award for Programming I

February 2017

Course Directors Award for Programming II

March 2017

Salutatorian

June 2017

Salutatorian is awarded to the graduate with the 2nd highest GPA in their class.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- C++ C# AI Programming
- Python Java Gameplay Systems
- Engines (Unity/DirectX) Networking MySQL Databases